



Gabriel Piloto Gonçalves

Nationality: Brazilian Date of birth: 23 Nov 1998

♥ Home: Triq-il-Ghajn 30-32 Corner Stone Residence 2 Apartment, SWQ3122 Swieqi (

Malta)

ABOUT ME

I'm from brazil, my native language is Portuguese, currently I'm working at my English that at moment is Intermediate, I arrived in Malta at November 5th. In Brazil I have worked as Administrative Officer assistant, Human resources Assistant, Warehouse manager, Fleet manager assistant and I had my own business, a Burger Joint. In these jobs I got experience in Office administration, Customer Support, Manager, Computer Skills, Microsoft Office proficient, Organizational Skills, Marketing Digital, Social media Content creator. I'm available for interviews and trial days.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Owner

ARTESANO BURGUERS [11 Jan 2020 - 31 Oct 2022]

City: PILAR DO SUL Country: Brazil

Owner, customer service, responsible for purchasing ingredients, price quotation from suppliers, preparing ingredients, testing product quality, grill man, responsible for order delivery logistics, payment of employees, cash control.

Fleet Manager assistant

IRMAOS CARVALHO TRANSPORTES LTDA [11 Jun 2018 - 10 Jan 2020]

City: PILAR DO SUL Country: Brazil

Trouble shooting of all fleet, tracking vehicles, organize schedule for trucks, direct contact with customers for any thing, purchase and receipt of fuel stock.

Manager of warehouse

IRMAOS CARVALHO TRANSPORTES LTDA [21 Oct 2016 – 10 Jun 2018]

City: PILAR DO SUL Country: Brazil

Keep the warehouse clean, organized and full, get budget of parts for trucks, cars and tools for a mechanical workshop, make orders, receive orders.

Human resources administrative assistant

IRMAOS CARVALHO TRANSPORTES LTDA [16 Mar 2014 - 20 Oct 2016]

City: PILAR DO SUL Country: Brazil

helping the manager of human resources to contract employee like organize papers, schedule medical exams, give instructions to employees training, etc.

Administrative office assistant

IRMÃOS CARVALHO TRANSPORTES LTDA [5 Mar 2013 – 15 Mar 2014]

City: PILAR DO SUL Country: Brazil

make and receive calls, write down messages, organize the office, Purchase office stuffs and purchase of personal safety equipment.

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Lawyer Student

Athon Ensino Superior Sorocaba [1 Feb 2018 - Current]

Address: R. da Penha, 1181, Centro Building, 18010-004 Sorocaba (Brazil)

Website: https://athonedu.com.br/

English Student

The English Club [20 Jan 2015 – 30 Mar 2016]

Address: Av. Américo Brasiliense, 391 - Centro Building, 18185-000 Pilar do Sul (Brazil)

High School

Escola Estadual Vereador Odilon Batista Jordão [1 Jan 2013 - 31 Dec 2015]

Address: Coronel Moraes Cunha building, 18185000 PILAR DO SUL (Brazil)

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Portuguese

Other language(s):

English

LISTENING B1 READING B1 WRITING B1

SPOKEN PRODUCTION B1 SPOKEN INTERACTION B1

DIGITAL SKILLS

Microsoft Excel (basic knowledge) / Microsoft Office / Microsoft Powerpoint / Microsoft Word / Skype / Facebook / Instagram / Google Docs / Outlook / Good listener and communicator / Motivated / Instagram advertisement